https://www.fptransitions.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices and notification policies for this site. If you have any questions, please call us at 800.934.3303.
We agree to notify you of or otherwise make you aware of:
All instances where personally identifiable information is collected from you through this site
The organization collecting the information
How the information is used
With whom, if anyone, the information may be shared
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you feel that our company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact us immediately by email at helpdesk@businesstrans.com.
Information Collection and Use
Business Transitions, LLC, dba FP Transitions, is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site. We sometimes use an Internet device called cookies to store login or other information on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard drive. Many Web sites use cookies to make your life as a Web user easier and more engaging. We use cookies to simplify your access or to tailor our services to your needs and interests. For some services, we offer users the choice of having an ID or password stored in a cookie. Cookies come with some protections. We do not store credit card numbers in cookies. No other Web site can read a cookie set by us. We cannot read a cookie that another Web site wrote to your computer. Most Internet browsers are set to accept cookies. Users can reset browsers to refuse cookies and still use our Web site, we occasionally offer users the opportunity to download useful documents, register for online seminars, communicate online with a customer support representative, or receive sales or promotional information for products and services of interest to them. A user who agrees may be asked to provide contact information (e.g., name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, and fax number) that we will use to respond to the request and to provide information about our products and services. If you are affiliated with a broker-dealer or custodian that is a member of an FP Transitions Corporate Program, you may be eligible for discounts; by accepting these discounts, you give FP Transitions permission to share your information with your broker-dealer / custodian.  We may from time to time use aggregate data collected to publish such data cumulatively, however, FP Transitions will not release any specific or identifiable information belonging to you without your written permission.
Registration
In order to use certain parts of our Web site, a user must first complete on-line registration forms. During their registration process a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. We do not sell or share this information in any commercial fashion except to publish the cumulative results in a statistical format that does not identify any individual or company.
Log Files
We use IP addresses and IDs to analyze trends, administer this Web site, track users' movement to prevent abuse, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use by FP Transitions.
Sharing
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal Information that can identify any individual person. We may partner with third parties to provide additional services to which the user may choose to subscribe. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, FP Transitions, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Surveys
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of improving the usability of our services and increasing user satisfaction.
Security
This service and web site take every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information, this information is protected both online and off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices and networks. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a system administrator or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. These employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a physically secure environment.
If you have any questions about the security of our service or web site, you can send an email to helpdesk@businesstrans.com.
Special Offers
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice/Opt-out section below.
Site and Service Updates
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support at helpdesk@businesstrans.com.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our service at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive occasional updates or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or at the URL contained in the email.
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.
© FP Transitions, LLC
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
4900 Meadows Suite 300 | Lake Oswego, OR 97035 | p. 800.934.3303 | f. 503.452.4205
